# **Kishore Patra**

**Frontend Developer** 

Email - patra.kishore65@gmail.com

Mobile - 9748591585

## **Career Objective**

To seek a better position in an organization which offers professional growth, together with a resourceful, innovative and flexible environment.

# **Summary**

Talented and experienced Information Technology professional having 4+ years of experience, with background in Front end Development. Extensive knowledge in development of interactive websites. Familiar with many web related programming languages, Frameworks, Themes, Tools etc. Hard working, detail oriented and able to do multi-task. Able to work with clients and users to determine requirements and formulate solutions. Excellent verbal and written communication skills.

## **Skills**

**Languages:** HTML5, CSS3, Javascript **Frameworks:** Angular 1.x/2/4/5/6/7

Libraries: React, Redux, RxJs

Themes: Shopify, Bigcommerce, Squarespace

Hybrid Mobile Technologies: React Native, IONIC, Cordova

Tools: VS Code

## **Experience**

Node Technologies (27-08-2018 - Present) Front end Developer

Techtree IT Systems Pvt. Ltd. (From 17-07- 2017 to 24-08-2018, 1 Year 1 Months) Front end Developer

Esolz Technologies (From 11-11- 2015 To 29-04-2017, 1 Year 5 Months) Front end Developer

Archtech Design (From 17-02- 2014 to 15-04- 2015, 1 Year 1 Month) Front end Developer

# **Projects**

## SalesGO Visits

Role: Hybrid Mobile App Developer

Tools: React Native, React, Redux, Realm DB, es6

**Duration: 4 Months** 

Play Store Link: <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.nodetech.salesgovisits&hl=en">https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.nodetech.salesgovisits&hl=en</a>

App Store Link: https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/salesgo-visits/id1018156841?ls=1&mt=8

#### Crotle

Role:Frontend Developer

Tools: Angular 7, Bootstrap, Angular Material HTML, CSS, REST Api

**Duration: Ongoing** 

Link: http://www.mytaskplus.com

#### Visit Dashboard

Role:Frontend Developer

Tools: React, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, REST Api

**Duration: Ongoing** 

Link: https://hdfc-dashboard.salesgovisits.com/

## Raine&Horne B2B

Role:Frontend Developer

Tools: Angular 5, Bootstrap, Angular Material, ngx-bootstrap, HTML, CSS, typescript, REST Api

**Duration: 6 Months** 

Link: http://14.142.204.102/login

## Club Apparel Admin

Role:Frontend Developer

Tools: AngularJs, HTML, CSS, jQuery, Javascript, JSON, Bootstrap

**Duration: 6 Months** 

Link: http://14.142.50.226/ClubApparel/

#### Nomisma Dashboard UI

Role:Frontend Developer

Tools: HTML, CSS, jQuery, Javascript, Bootstrap

**Duration: 1 Month** 

Link: https://esolz.co.in/lab5/html/nomisma/dashboard.html

### **Mutual Fund**

Role: Frontend Developer

Tools: HTML, CSS, jQuery, Javascript, Bootstrap

**Duration: 3 Months** 

Link: https://esolz.co.in/lab5/html/mutual-fund/goal-planning-dashboard.html

## **Mobinspire**

Role: Frontend Developer

Tools: HTML, CSS, jQuery, Javascript, Bootstrap

Duration: 1 Month

Link: <a href="https://esolz.co.in/lab5/html/mobinspire/">https://esolz.co.in/lab5/html/mobinspire/</a>

#### Raytheon

Role: Frontend Developer

Tools: HTML, CSS, jQuery, Javascript, Bootstrap

Duration: 15 days

Link: https://esolz.co.in/lab5/html/raytheon/

#### **Facelift**

Role: Frontend Developer

Tools: HTML, CSS, jQuery, Javascript, Bootstrap, SCSS

Duration: 15 days

Link: <a href="https://esolz.co.in/lab5/html/facelifit/">https://esolz.co.in/lab5/html/facelifit/</a>

#### Student Management System

Role: Frontend Developer

Tools: AngularJs, HTML, CSS, jQuery, Javascript

**Duration: 3 Months** 

Link: http://site.area51.pe/student-management/

# All other Projects Link

## **Interactive UI:**

https://esolz.co.in/lab5/html/uber-conf/

#### IONIC

https://esolz.co.in/lab5/html/ionic-app/#/app/login

#### Shopify

- https://sendsomething-new.myshopify.com/
- https://bareblow-development.myshopify.com/
- https://www.matchamate.com/

## **Education**

10th - Sagore Dutt Free High School (2009)

Higher Secondary - Ariadaha Kalachand High School (2011)

Graduation - B. Com(Hons.), Prasanta Chandra Mahalanavis Mahavidyalay (2014)

# **Hobbies**

Playing Football, Playing Carrom, Internet Surfing, Watching Youtube Video, Listening Song

## **Personal Profile**

Date of Birth - 16th Nov, 1993

Marital Status - Unmarried

Language Known - Bengali, Hindi, English

Nationality - Indian

## **Declaration**

I hereby declare that all the above given particulars and details are true to the best of my knowledge and belief and I am also willing to give my best for the company.